<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Container>
	<Name>batchcutencode</Name>
	<Beta>False</Beta>
	<Category>MediaServer:Video</Category>
	<Overview>batchcutencode will re-encode recorded videos to conserve storage space.  It was originally developed to re-encode videos from either DVR's such as mythtv, plex DVR, or playon.</Overview>

	<Description>batchcutencode will re-encode recorded videos.  It uses HandBrake for the conversion and currently only will process mp4/mkv/avi/ts to mp4.[br]
	This docker will create (by default) a share called transcode.  Create 3 directories in the share (cut, encode, complete), and optionally, you can create a defaultsettings.txt file.[br]
	[br]
	Once the docker is started, files can be copied into the cut or encode directories.  They will be automatically detected and the processing will be kicked off.  If files are copied in the directories prior to teh docker starting, they will not be detected.[br]
	[br]
	The defaultsettings.txt file allows you to override environment variables set in the UNRAID docker configuration.  These setting will apply without the docker being restarted.  They will apply to the next file that is processed.  This file is placed in the transcode directory at the same level as the cut, encode, and complete directories[br]
	[br]
	Directories:[br]
	cut directory - videos will have 5 seconds (by default) cut off the beginning and end, and then be moved to the encode directory.[br]
	encode directory - videos will be re-encoded using HandBrake's presets.  [br]
	complete directory - videos that have completed encoding[br]
	[br]
	Variables:[br]
	* SECONDS_FRONT: seconds to be cut off beginning of video.  must be an integer.  Default is 5 seconds[br]
	* SECONDS_END: seconds to be cut off end of video.  must be an integer.  Default is 5 seconds[br]
	* ENCODE_PROFILE: Handbrake encoding profile to use.  Custom profiles are not possible.[br]
	"Very Fast 1080p30"[br]
	"Fast 1080p30"[br]
	"HQ 1080p30 Surround"[br]
	"Super HQ 1080p30 Surround"[br]
	[br]
	[br]
	Example defaultsettings.txt file:[br]
	# Using this overides the settings in the UNRAID Docker Settings GUI.[br]
	# These settings are sourced before each file is processed and can therfor be changed on the fly.[br]
	# (Blank Lines in this file can cause issues if file created in windows - windows newline issue)[br]
	# This will disable the encoding and only do a cut.  Cut files will be placed in the encode directory, but not be processed when this is enabled.[br]
	#CUT_ONLY="YES"[br]
	# Defines how many seconds to cut off of the front and back of the video.  Default for both is 5 seconds[br]
	#export SECONDS_FRONT=5[br]
	#export SECONDS_END=5[br]
	# Defines the handbrake encoding file.  Choose one.  Default is "Fast 1080p30"[br]
	#export ENCODE_PROFILE="Fast 1080p30"[br]
	#export ENCODE_PROFILE="Very Fast 1080p30"[br]
	#export ENCODE_PROFILE="HQ 1080p30 Surround"[br]
	#export ENCODE_PROFILE="Super HQ 1080p30 Surround"[br]
	[br]
	[br]

	</Description>
	<Change></Change>
	<Support></Support>
	<Registry>https://hub.docker.com/r/rupeypirate/batchcutencode/</Registry>
	<Repository>rupeypirate/batchcutencode</Repository>
	<BindTime>true</BindTime>
	<Privileged>false</Privileged>
	<Networking>
		<Mode>bridge</Mode>
		<Publish>
		<Port>
		</Port>
		</Publish>
	</Networking>
	<Environment>
		<Variable>
			<Name>ENCODE_PROFILE</Name>
			<Value>Fast 1080p30</Value>
		</Variable>		
		<Variable>
			<Name>SECONDS_FRONT</Name>
			<Value>5</Value>
		</Variable>
		<Variable>
			<Name>SECONDS_END</Name>
			<Value>5</Value>
		</Variable>
	</Environment>
	<Data>
		<Volume>
			<HostDir>/mnt/user/transcode</HostDir>
			<ContainerDir>/transcode</ContainerDir>
			<Mode>rw</Mode>
		</Volume> 
	</Data>
	<WebUI></WebUI>
	<Banner></Banner>
	<Icon>https://i.imgur.com/Se6akqo.png</Icon>
</Container>